https://www.abcsofattraction.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Get Started
Free Training Video
Privacy Policy
The ABCs of Attraction is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to The ABCs of Attraction Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using The ABCs of Attraction website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
The ABCs of Attraction collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. The ABCs of Attraction also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by The ABCs of Attraction. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by The ABCs of Attraction for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of The ABCs of Attraction Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through The ABCs of Attraction public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: The ABCs of Attraction does not read any of your private online communications.
The ABCs of Attraction encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from The ABCs of Attraction so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. The ABCs of Attraction is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of The ABCs of Attraction and The ABCs of Attraction family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
The ABCs of Attraction collects and uses your personal information to operate The ABCs of Attraction Web site and deliver the services you have requested. The ABCs of Attraction also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The ABCs of Attraction and its affiliates. The ABCs of Attraction may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
The ABCs of Attraction does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. The ABCs of Attraction may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, The ABCs of Attraction may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The ABCs of Attraction, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
The ABCs of Attraction does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
The ABCs of Attraction keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within The ABCs of Attraction, in order to determine what The ABCs of Attraction services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within The ABCs of Attraction to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
The ABCs of Attraction Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The ABCs of Attraction or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The ABCs of Attraction; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The ABCs of Attraction, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The ABCs of Attraction Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize The ABCs of Attraction pages, or register with The ABCs of Attraction site or services, a cookie helps The ABCs of Attraction to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same The ABCs of Attraction Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use The ABCs of Attraction features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the The ABCs of Attraction services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
The ABCs of Attraction secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The ABCs of Attraction secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
The ABCs of Attraction will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The ABCs of Attraction encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how The ABCs of Attraction is protecting your information.
Contact Information
The ABCs of Attraction welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The ABCs of Attraction has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The ABCs of Attraction at support@abcofattraction.com.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
SPEND time getting your questions answered in our FAQ!
READ FAQ
